onlinesuccesswithchris.com 2018-05-24

# Privacy Policy | Online Success With Chris

We are committed to safeguarding the privacy of our website visitors; this policy sets out how we will treat your personal information.

**(1) What information do we collect?**

We may collect, store and use the following kinds of personal data:

(a) information about your visits to and use of this website;

(b) information about any transactions carried out between you and us on or in relation to this website, including information relating to any purchases you make of our goods or services;

(c) information that you provide to us for the purpose of registering with us and/or subscribing to our website services and/or email notifications; and

(d) OTHER INFORMATION.

**(2) Information about website visits**

We may collect information about your computer and your visits to this website such as your IP address, geographical location, browser type, referral source, length of visit and number of page views. We may use this information in the administration of this website, to improve the website’s usability, and for marketing purposes.

We use cookies on this website. A cookie is a text file sent by a web server to a web browser, and stored by the browser. The text file is then sent back to the server each time the browser requests a page from the server. This enables the web server to identify and track the web browser.

We may send a cookie which may be stored on by your browser on your computer’s hard drive. We may use the information we obtain from the cookie in the administration of this website, to improve the website’s usability and for marketing purposes. We may also use that information to recognize your computer when you visit our website, and to personalize our website for you. [Our advertisers, if any, may also send you cookies.]

Most browsers allow you to refuse to accept cookies. (For example, in Internet Explorer you can refuse all cookies by clicking “Tools”, “Internet Options”, “Privacy”, and selecting “Block all cookies” using the sliding selector.) This will, however, have a negative impact upon the usability of many websites, including this one.

**(3) Using personal data**

Personal data submitted on this website will be used for the purposes specified in this privacy policy or in relevant parts of the website. In addition to the uses identified elsewhere in this privacy policy, we may use your personal information to:

(a) improve your browsing experience by personalizing the website;

(b) send information (other than marketing communications) to you which we think may be of interest to you by post or by email or similar technology;

(c) send to you marketing communications relating to our business which we think may be of interest to you by post or, where you have specifically agreed to this, by email or similar technology (you can inform us at any time if you no longer require marketing communications to be sent by clicking 'Unsubscribe' at the bottom of any email you receive from us)

(e) OTHER USES.

We will not, without your express consent, provide your personal information to any third parties for the purpose of direct marketing.

**(4) Other disclosures**

In addition to the disclosures reasonably necessary for the purposes identified elsewhere in this privacy policy, we may disclose information about you:

(a) to the extent that we are required to do so by law;

(b) in connection with any legal proceedings or prospective legal proceedings;

(c) in order to establish, exercise or defend our legal rights (including providing information to others for the purposes of fraud prevention and reducing credit risk); and

Except as provided in this privacy policy, we will not provide your information to third parties.

**(5) International data transfers**

Information that we collect may be stored and processed in and transferred between any of the countries in which we operate in order to enable us to use the information in accordance with this privacy policy.

If you are in the European Union, information which you provide may be transferred to countries (including the United States and Japan) which do not have data protection laws equivalent to those in force in the European Union. By using our site you expressly agree to such transfers.

**(6) Security of your personal data**

We will take reasonable precautions to prevent the loss, misuse or alteration of your personal information. Of course, data transmission over the internet is inherently insecure, and we cannot guarantee the security of data sent over the Internet.

We will store all the personal information you provide on our secure servers. All electronic transactions you make to or receive from us will be encrypted using SSL technology.

You are responsible for keeping your password confidential. **We will never ask you for your password.** If our support staff is required to access an account in your name on one of our websites, as part of their troubleshooting, they are required to obtain your permission in writing to do so, first. Once you grant our staff member your permission to access your account, they will change the password on the account, in order to login, then complete their diagnostics. When this is done you will be issued a new password. Then the support staff will then require that you change your password the next time you login, to protect the confidentiality of the passwords you choose.

We do not store any of your credit card information on this website, or on any website which is owned and operated by CJ Success Team LLC. All credit card information you provide on our secure severs is passed directly to our secure 3rd party shopping cart which uses industry standard 128 bit secure sockets layer (SSL) technology to encrypt sensitive information such as your credit card and other financial information. This includes the credit card number, expiry date, and billing address.

**(7) Policy amendments**

We may update this privacy policy from time-to-time by posting a new version on our website. You should check this page occasionally to ensure you are happy with any changes.

We may also notify you of changes to our privacy policy be email.

**(8) Third party websites**

The website contains links to other websites. We are not responsible for the privacy policies of third party websites.

**(9) Contact**

You can contact us at [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#6203060f0b0c220d0c0e0b0c0711170101071111150b160a010a100b114c010d0f) for 'general' site use and website information questions ONLY. Please allow 48-72 hours for a response to your question from our website support staff (this is a voluntary response guarantee). For faster service, if you need technical assistance, or have issues or questions regarding a product purchase we must request that you use our [_Support Desk_](http://cjsuccessteam.net/support/) link to open a service ticket.  

In this manner we are able to track both our progress in servicing your issue(s) and your feedback to us on the matter. Using these methods we are constantly doing our best to address the needs of our customers. Thank you.

**Or submit a ticket to our Support Desk at:**

We try to respond to tickets with 24-48 hours, but during new product roll-outs, periods of high traffic volume, inclement weather events affecting staffing, etc. our response time period may be further delayed.
